Yes
Ừ
[music]
[âm nhạc]
if there are times when we talk about
nếu có những lúc nói về
words from the heart wanting to find peace, wanting to
từ trong tâm muốn tìm Yên Bình theo muốn
illuminate the soul,
soi sáng tâm hồn
then temporarily leave the deep city, the three
thì tạm xa nơi thành phố sâu bộ kết ba
holes, so my friend, let's meet at the summer retreat
lỗ nên bạn ơi ta gặp nhau khóa tu mùa hè
from all corners of the world, coming back to life, to cultivate the
từ khắp muôn Cương đến về đời
heart when the pain of the past is gone, the people who once
nơi Tu tâm khi gian cơn đau người từng
worked in the past, the moonlit night is where
làm trong gian xưa đêm trăng là nơi
we still connect, you come here to find us, we
chúng tôi vẫn kết nối anh về đây tìm ta
know joy, don't want to be together,
biết vui không muốn bên cùng nhau hãy
come here
đến đây
together, connect, love, my past,
cùng nhau kết nối yêu thương quá khứ của
together, this [
em cùng nhau Này phát
music]
[âm nhạc]
more than the past, friendship,
hơn quá khứ tình bạn ạ
I remember the neighborhood, just yesterday we met, we
a nhớ phường Mới hôm nào
just cleaned up, waiting until now, so
nhận bên nhau chỉ dọn Câu Chờ đến nay
many things have happened,
thì đã bao điều
sitting together, we will share our hearts, here,
cùng ngồi bên nhau sẽ chia tấm mình đây
backpack, my friend,
ba lô lên bạn ơi
far apart, we are similar, summer retreat,
xa giống nhau con tu mùa hè
corner, wanting love, coming back to the
góc muốn thương đến về đến
place, I am in the war, in the midst of the storm, like
nơi tôi trong cuộc chiến giữa cơn như
hands, pure, not yet in,
từng tay trong sáng chưa đến trong
we come back
là chúng tôi
here when
về đây khi
happy, don't want scars, we have come together, come to
vui không muốn sẹo đã cùng nhau hay đến
the Place of Love, connecting, love,
Nơi Tình Yêu Kết nối yêu thương hoạt
mother's activities together forever, a
động của mẹ cùng nhau hoài h a
happy [music] things, remember, drinking in the body, the air force,
vui bên nhớ uống trong thể không quân
more than forgetting, like bamboo together, transmitting
hơn quên sao như trúc bên nhau truyền
to people when the child is on with business, about the
sang người khi con trên với buôn bán về
love still  not paying attention,
mối tình vẫn không để ý
uhuh
ừ ừ
[music] uh uh
[âm nhạc]